{
    "sets": {
        "Hour1": [
            {
    "question": "TCP/IP standards?",
    "answer": "System of rules defining communications on TCP/IP network"
  },
  {
    "question": "TCP/IP Implementation?",
    "answer": "Software components that enable the hardware to perform functions that participate in TCP/IP network."
  },
  {
    "question": "TCP/IP 2 important features?",
    "answer": "1- End-node verification.\n2- Dynamic routing."
  },
  {
    "question": "RFC?",
    "answer": "The Technical papers that serve as the official documentation for TCP/IP made by researchers and workgroups that try to improve the TCP/IP protocol."
  },
  {
    "question": "IAB?",
    "answer": "Internet Architecture Board (the administration)."
  },
  {
    "question": "IETF?",
    "answer": "Internet Engineering Task Force (researchers)."
  },
  {
    "question": "IRTF?",
    "answer": "Internet Research Task Force (sponsors)."
  },
  {
    "question": "ICANN?",
    "answer": "Internet Corporation For Assigned Names & Numbers."
  }
        ],
        "Hour2": [
            {
    "question": "TCP/IP responsibilities?",
    "answer": "1- Dividing messages into chunks.\n2- Interfacing with network hardware adapter.\n3- Addressing distant specific device.\n4- Routing data to subnets.\n5- Error & Flow control, ACK.\n6- Accept data from app and pass it to network.\n7- Receive data from network and pass it to app."
  },
  {
    "question": "Encapsulation?",
    "answer": "Each layer on the sending machine adds a header with information that would help the layer on the receiving machine interpret data."
  },
  {
    "question": "TCP/IP model layers?",
    "answer": "1- App Layer.\n2- Transport Layer.\n3- Internet Layer.\n4- Network Access Layer."
  },
  {
    "question": "App Layer role?",
    "answer": "1- Enables programs written for OS environment to access the network.\n2- Provides apps for troubleshooting, file transfer, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "Transport Layer Role?",
    "answer": "Error & Flow Control, Acknowledgment."
  },
  {
    "question": "Internet Layer Role?",
    "answer": "1- Logical, hardware-independent addressing.\n2- Relates physical address to logical address (ARP).\n3- Provides routing to reduce traffic."
  },
  {
    "question": "Network Access Layer role?",
    "answer": "1- Interface with network hardware.\n2- Formats data for transmission.\n3- Address data based on MACs.\n4- Error control.\n5- Link data transmission with the correct access method."
  },
  {
    "question": "OSI model layers?",
    "answer": "1- App Layer.\n2- Presentation Layer.\n3- Session Layer.\n4- Transport Layer.\n5- Network Layer.\n6- Data Link Layer.\n7- Physical Layer."
  },
  {
    "question": "Presentation Layer role?",
    "answer": "1- Data encryption.\n2- Data compression.\n3- Translates data to standard format."
  },
  {
    "question": "Session Layer role?",
    "answer": "Manages sessions between communicating apps."
  },
  {
    "question": "Data Link Layer role?",
    "answer": "1- Interface to hardware.\n2- Maintain logical links for subnets."
  },
  {
    "question": "Physical Layer role?",
    "answer": "Converts data to a stream of electric/analog pulses."
  },
  {
    "question": "App Layer package name?",
    "answer": "Message."
  },
  {
    "question": "Transport Layer package name?",
    "answer": "- Segment (TCP)\n- Datagram (UDP)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Internet Layer package name?",
    "answer": "Datagram."
  },
  {
    "question": "Network Access Layer package name?",
    "answer": "Frame."
  },
  {
    "question": "TCP qualities?",
    "answer": "- Guarantees the delivery of data.\n- Error & Flow control.\n- Slow."
  },
  {
    "question": "UDP qualities?",
    "answer": "- Unreliable (doesn't guarantee data delivery).\n- Fast.\n- Offloads error & flow control to app layer."
  }
        ],
        "Hour3": [
            {
    "question": "Data Link Layer functions?",
    "answer": "- Media Access Control (MAC)\n- Logical Link Control (LLC)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Architectures of Network Access Layer?",
    "answer": "- IEEE 802.3 (Ethernet)\n- IEEE 802.11 (Wireless)\n- IEEE 802.16 (WiMax cellular)\n- PPP (Point-To-Point protocol)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Network Architecture Specifications?",
    "answer": "- Access method.\n- Data frame format.\n- Cabling type.\n- Cabling rules."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ethernet Qualities?",
    "answer": "- Inexpensive & Easily installed.\n- Uses (CSMA/CD) access method.\n- Good for light-moderate use.\n- Switches manage traffic to reduce collision."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ethernet Frame components?",
    "answer": "- Preamble (beginning of frame).\n- Recipient address.\n- Source address.\n- Optional VLAN tag.\n- Length (size of data).\n- Data.\n- FCS (Frame check sequence) using CRC (cyclical redundancy check)."
  }
        ]
    }
}
